hupso.com 2018-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Hupso.com

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

### Your Consent

By using this website, widgets (share buttons) or tools, you consent to our [Privacy Policy](http://www.hupso.com/privacy) and to our [Terms of Use](http://www.hupso.com/terms). 

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Hupso.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files may include, but not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, cookies, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to information that is personally identifiable (your name, your address, your email). We may disclose certain information and share log data with third parties for behavioral advertising, industry analysis, demographic profiling, and other purposes.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Hupso.com, widgets and tools may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser including, but not limited to, IP address, web browser version, operating sistem, time of visit. By using our widgets (share buttons) on other websites, you may be required (in certain countries) to obtain explicit permission from your visitors for using third-party cookies.

### Third Party Cookies

Some of our partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site or inside our widgets (share buttons). They automatically receive your IP address, URL, user-agent and other data when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see or to gather other statistics.

Hupso.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Hupso.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. To opt out of information collection by NAI members for targeted advertising [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). To opt out from receiving cookies from our share buttons click [here](http://www.hupso.com/share/cookies).

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Hupso.com may revise this privacy policy at any time without notice. By using this website, widgets (share buttons) or tools you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of this privacy policy.
